Ralph Jason Martinez Cadeliña

Peñaranda St. Brgy. Taft., Surigao City, PH 8400
+63 9705368194 ralphcadelina5@gmail.com
in linkedin.com/in/ralphcadelina

Notice period: 30 days

OBJECTIVE:

With a bachelor's degree holder in Information Technology with experience in the IT Industry particularly in Web Development. Conducted trainings as part of my professional career. I venture in securing a position in a company where I can apply my experience that would best fit my qualifications. I aim to further enhance my values toward any responsibility that I will undertake, develop my talents and skills for a continuous career improvement and excel in every way to tap my potentials, making a highly competent, assertive, proactive and creative individual.

EXPERTISE:

FUNCTIONAL & TECHNICAL SKILLS:

- o Software Engineering
- o Design & Architecture
- o Implementation

- o Configuration & Optimization
- o Security & Monitoring
- o RCA (Root Cause Analysis)

Software Development Skills:

- Web Development
 - o HTML5
 - o CSS
 - Bootstrap
 - Tailwind
 - JavaScript
 - o React JS
 - o Material UI
 - o Firebase
 - Git and Github
 - Node JS
 - API Integration (REST API)
 - o PHP
 - o Laravel

Server Administration Skills:

- > SERVERS (Windows Server 2008/2012)
- Microsoft Office (365, Word, Excel, Powerpoint, Access & Outlook)
- Database Management (MySQL)
- Computer Hardware & Software (Install, Repair, Troubleshoot, Sales & Maintenance)

WORK EXPERIENCE:

KodeGo

Position: Full Stack Developer (Bootcamp Trainee)

Duration: Nov 2022 - Feb 2023

Kre8tib I.T. Services

Position: Front-End Developer(Project-based)

Duration: Aug 2022 – Oct 2022

Responsibilities as Front-End Developer

Build and implements static web pages and email templates.

Surigao Education Center

Position: **Web Developer**Duration: Nov 2021- May 2022 **Responsibilities as Web Developer**

- o Build and maintain the official domain and subdomain of the institution.
- o Optimization and enhancement of website.
- o Conducts collaboration meetings weekly for point estimations.
- o Coordinates with staff and development team in every project.
- o Implement process, workflow, design and architecture.

Position: Data Encoder (Project based)

Duration: Jun 2021-Oct 2021

Responsibilities as Data Encoder (Project based)

o Integrates books information into the online library system.

Position: **Data Encoder (Intern)** Duration: Sep 2021-Feb 2021

Responsibilities as Data Encoder (Intern)

o Encode and edit equipment inventory for audit purposes.

PERSONAL PARTICULARS:

DOB: Jan 7, 1991
Marital Status: Single
Nationality: Filipino
Gender: Male

EDUCATION:

College: SURIGAO EDUCATION CENTER

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

Surigao City, Philippines

CHARACTER OF REFERENCE:

MARK MON E. MONTEROS

DevOps Engineer - HCL Technologies

Home: B2 L2 Ideal Homes, Butuan City PH 8600

Email: monteros.markmon@gmail.com

Contact #: +63 917 120 1973